https://www.travelplanners.co.uk/privacy-policy

GET A FAST QUOTE >>
Cookie Settings
to book your next holiday call us on
020 3542 8888
our travelplanners are waiting to assist you or visit our retail offices at Unit 2, Loughton Business Centre, Langston Road, Essex IG10 3SJ
HomeHoliday Types
Family HolidaysLuxury HolidaysMotorhome HolidaysVilla Package HolidaysHotel HolidaysCondo & Apartment HolidaysTwin Centre HolidaysMulti Centre HolidaysCruise & Stay DealsFly DriveEscorted TouringDestinations
DisneyOrlandoKissimmeeUniversalGulf CoastRest of FloridaThe Deep South, USACaliforniaCanadaDubaiNew YorkLas Vegas & NevadaHawaii HolidaysMore USAMexicoCaribbeanDestination FocusExclusive OffersLuxury CaribbeanExtras
Attraction TicketsBritish AirwaysCar HireCruise America MotorhomesMy Ultimate Las VegasThe SeaWorld ParksOnline Check-InSimon ShoppingUnited AirlinesVoyager Travel InsuranceOur ReviewsBlogCaribbean Collection
How we use your personal information
Last updated 25th May 2018.
Your information will be held by USAirtours Holidays (UK) Ltd and its trading companies, Travelplanners and Tailor Made Cruise Holidays
How we use your personal information
This privacy notice is to let you know how companies within the Group promise to look after your personal information. This includes what you tell us about yourself, what we learn by having you as a customer, and the choices you give us about what marketing you want us to send you. This notice explains how we do this and tells you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.
Our Privacy Promise
We promise:
To keep your data safe and private.
Not to sell your data
This notice sets out a summary of your rights under General Data Protection Act 2018.
How the law protects you
As well as our Privacy Promise, your privacy is protected by law. This section explains how that works.
Data Protection law says that we are allowed to use personal information only if we have a proper reason to do so. This includes sharing it outside with third parties. The law says we must have one or more of these reasons:
To fulfil a contract we have with you, or
When it is our legal duty, or
When it is in our legitimate interest, or
When you consent to it.
A legitimate interest is when we have a business or commercial reason to use your information. But even then, it must not unfairly go against what is right and best for you. If we rely on our legitimate interest, we will tell you what that is.
Here is a list of all the ways that we may use your personal information, and which of the reasons we rely on to do so. This is also where we tell you what our legitimate interests are.
What we use your personal information for
Our reasons
Our legitimate interests
Manage our relationship with you or your business
Fulfilling contracts
Your consent
Our legitimate interests
Our legal duty
Keeping records up to date
Working out which of our products and services may interest you and telling you about them
Being efficient about how we fulfil our legal duties
To develop and manage our Brands, products and services
Fulfilling contracts
Our legitimate interests
Our legal duty
Being efficient about our how we fulfil our legal duties
To detect, investigate, report, and seek to prevent financial crime
To manage risk for us and our customers
To obey laws and regulations that apply to us
To respond to complaints and seek to resolve them
Fulfilling contracts
Our legitimate interests
Our legal duty
Developing and improving how we deal with financial crime, as well as doing our legal duties in this respect
Complying with regulations that apply to us
Being efficient about how we fulfil our legal and contractual duties
To run our business in an efficient and proper way. This includes managing our financial position, business capability, planning, communications, corporate governance, and audit
Our legitimate interests
Our legal duty
Complying with regulations that apply to us
Being efficient about how we fulfil our legal and contractual duties
To exercise our rights set out in agreements or contracts
Fulfilling contracts
Types of personal Information
Financial – Bank details , Card details
Contact – Where you live and how to contact you
Contractual – Details of the products and services we provide you.
Documentary data – Passports, Drivers Licence, Utility Bill
Transactional – details of payments between you and us
Social relationships – Your family and friends
Special Types – Dates of birth , Health data
Consents – How you would like us to contact you ie email
Where we collect personal information from
Data you give to us
When you talk to us on the phone
Complete online registration forms
Complete online enquiry forms via a websites
Complete application forms
Take part in competitions/surveys
Complete feedback forms
Who we share your data with
Suppliers deemed necessary by us to perform our agreement/contract with you.
Credit/Debit card Merchant processors
Any third party deemed necessary to conform with our regulatory/statutory and legal duties
We may be required to share your data with Insurance companies in the event of a claim by us or yourselves
Marketing
We may contact you through our ‘marketing’ communication by email, post or phone to tell you about relevant products and offers
The personal information we hold is made up of what you tell us, and data we collect when you use our services, or from third parties we work with.
We study this to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you.
We will continue to communicate with you regarding either existing travel bookings or relevant future offers that we believe will be in both your legitimate interest and ours.
You can ask us to stop sending you marketing messages by using the ‘unsubscribe’ option on our emails or contacting us at any time.
How long we keep your personal information
We will keep your personal information for a period of up to six years
To respond to any questions or complaints.
To show that we treated you fairly.
To maintain records according to rules that apply to us.
We may keep your data for longer than six years if we cannot delete it for legal, regulatory or technical reasons.
How to get a copy of the personal data we hold
Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Write to: J Frowd
Data Protection Officer
USAirtours Holidays (UK) Ltd
2 Loughton Business Centre
Langston Road
Loughton
Essex
IG10 3SJ
You have the right to object to our use of your personal information, or to ask us to delete, remove, or stop using your personal information if there is no need for us to keep it. This is known as the ‘right to object’ and ‘right to erasure’, or the ‘right to be forgotten’.
There may be legal or other official reasons why we need to keep or use your data. But please tell us if you think that we should not be using it
How to withdraw your consent
You can withdraw your consent at any time. Please contact us if you want to do so.
GET A FAST QUOTE >>
or to book your next holiday call us on
020 3542 8888
our travelplanners are waiting to assist you
Pack Peace of Mind
FREE FAST QUOTE
Complete your details in less than 60 seconds and receive your holiday quote from your personal expert travel advisor within 24 hours.
×
Submission Preview
…
Close
Personal Details
First Name*
Last Name*
Email Address*
Home Number
Contact Number*
Holiday Type*- Please Select -Villa HolidayHotel HolidayCondo/Apartment HolidayTwin CentreMulti Centre HolidayCruise and StayFly DriveHoliday Details
Destination 1*- Please Select -CaliforniaCaribbeanFloridaHawaiiLas VegasNew YorkOther
California*- Please Select -Los AngelesSan DiegoSan FranciscoOther
Caribbean*- Please Select -ArubaAntiguaBahamasBarbadosCubaDominican RepublicGrand Cayman IslandsJamaicaMexicoSt LuciaSt MartinSt ThomasOther
Florida*- Please Select -OrlandoFlorida KeysGulf CoastMiamiOther
Orlando*- Please Select -Disney Area VillasKissimmeeLake Buena VistaInternational DriveUniversalWalt Disney World ResortOther/Any
Gulf Coast*- Please Select -Anna Maria IslandBradentonFort MyersMarco IslandNaplesSanibel/CaptivaSarasotaSt Petes/ClearwaterOther/Any
Hawaii*- Please Select -Oahu/WaikikiKauaiMauiKona/HiloMolokaiLanaiOther/Any
Number of Nights*- Please Select -71412345689101112131516171819202122232425262728
Destination 2*- Please Select -CaliforniaCaribbeanFloridaHawaiiLas VegasNew YorkOther
California*- Please Select -Los AngelesSan DiegoSan FranciscoOther
Caribbean*- Please Select -ArubaAntiguaBahamasBarbadosCubaDominican RepublicGrand Cayman IslandsJamaicaMexicoSt LuciaSt MartinSt ThomasOther
Florida*- Please Select -OrlandoFlorida KeysGulf CoastMiamiOther
Orlando*- Please Select -Disney Area VillasKissimmeeLake Buena VistaInternational DriveUniversalWalt Disney World ResortOther/Any
Gulf Coast*- Please Select -Anna Maria IslandBradentonFort MyersMarco IslandNaplesSanibel/CaptivaSarasotaSt Petes/ClearwaterOther/Any
Hawaii*- Please Select -Oahu/WaikikiKauaiMauiKona/HiloMolokaiLanaiOther/Any
Number of Nights*- Please Select -71412345689101112131516171819202122232425262728
Destination 3*- Please Select -CaliforniaCaribbeanFloridaHawaiiLas VegasNew YorkOther
California*- Please Select -Los AngelesSan DiegoSan FranciscoOther
Caribbean*- Please Select -ArubaAntiguaBahamasBarbadosCubaDominican RepublicGrand Cayman IslandsJamaicaMexicoSt LuciaSt MartinSt ThomasOther
Florida*- Please Select -OrlandoFlorida KeysGulf CoastMiamiOther
Orlando*- Please Select -Disney Area VillasKissimmeeLake Buena VistaInternational DriveUniversalWalt Disney World ResortOther/Any
Gulf Coast*- Please Select -Anna Maria IslandBradentonFort MyersMarco IslandNaplesSanibel/CaptivaSarasotaSt Petes/ClearwaterOther/Any
Hawaii*- Please Select -Oahu/WaikikiKauaiMauiKona/HiloMolokaiLanaiOther/Any
Number of Nights*- Please Select -71412345689101112131516171819202122232425262728
Destination 4- Please Select -CaliforniaCaribbeanFloridaHawaiiLas VegasNew YorkOther
California- Please Select -Los AngelesSan DiegoSan FranciscoOther
Caribbean- Please Select -ArubaAntiguaBahamasBarbadosCubaDominican RepublicGrand Cayman IslandsJamaicaMexicoSt LuciaSt MartinSt ThomasOther
Florida- Please Select -OrlandoFlorida KeysGulf CoastMiamiOther
Orlando- Please Select -Disney Area VillasKissimmeeLake Buena VistaInternational DriveUniversalWalt Disney World ResortOther/Any
Gulf Coast- Please Select -Anna Maria IslandBradentonFort MyersMarco IslandNaplesSanibel/CaptivaSarasotaSt Petes/ClearwaterOther/Any
Hawaii- Please Select -Oahu/WaikikiKauaiMauiKona/HiloMolokaiLanaiOther/Any
Number of Nights- Please Select -71412345689101112131516171819202122232425262728
Destination 5- Please Select -CaliforniaCaribbeanFloridaHawaiiLas VegasNew YorkOther
California- Please Select -Los AngelesSan DiegoSan FranciscoOther
Caribbean- Please Select -ArubaAntiguaBahamasBarbadosCubaDominican RepublicGrand Cayman IslandsJamaicaMexicoSt LuciaSt MartinSt ThomasOther
Florida- Please Select -OrlandoFlorida KeysGulf CoastMiamiOther
Orlando- Please Select -Disney Area VillasKissimmeeLake Buena VistaInternational DriveUniversalWalt Disney World ResortOther/Any
Gulf Coast- Please Select -Anna Maria IslandBradentonFort MyersMarco IslandNaplesSanibel/CaptivaSarasotaSt Petes/ClearwaterOther/Any
Hawaii- Please Select -Oahu/WaikikiKauaiMauiKona/HiloMolokaiLanaiOther/Any
Number of Nights- Please Select -71412345689101112131516171819202122232425262728
Cruise Duration*- Please Select -734561014
Cruise Type*- Please Select -Alaskan CruiseCaribbean CruiseHawaiian CruiseMexico CruiseTransatlanticOther
Holiday Duration (Nights)*- Please Select -714345689101112131516171819202122232425262728
Preferred Cruise Line- Please Select -AzamaraCarnival CruisesCelebrity CruisesCunardDisney Cruise LineHolland America LineP&O CruisesPrincess CruisesRoyal CaribbeanNorwegian Cruise LineSilverseaExclusive Offers
Static ContentExtra Information
Flexibility (Days)*- Please Select -Not Flexible+/- 1+/- 3+/- 5+/- 7+/- 14
Departure Airport*- Please Select -AberdeenBelfastBirminghamBournemouthBristolCardiffDublinEast MidlandsEdinburghGlasgowHumbersideInvernessLeeds/BradfordLondon (Any)London GatwickLondon HeathrowManchesterNewcastleTeeside
Cabin Class- Please Select -EconomyEnhanced EconomyBusiness ClassUpper/First Class
Departure Date*
Transportation*- Please Select -Car HireTransfersNone
Number of Adults*- Please Select -123456789101112131415
Number of Children- Please Select -123456789
Child 1 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 2 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 3 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 4 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 5 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 6 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 7 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 8 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
Child 9 Age- Please Select -12345678910111213141516
What sort of holiday are you looking for?*- Please Select -BudgetModerateLuxuryExclusive Offers
Please add any comments that you feel may help your TravelPlanner find you the best quality value for money itinerary available
UTM Source
UTM Campaign
Processed
WebsiteTravelplanners
PREV
NEXT
PREVIEW Reset
SUBMIT QUOTE REQUEST >>
Top Cruise & Stay Deals
from £789pp
SEE MORE DETAIL...
California
from £599pp
SEE MORE DETAIL...
Rest of Florida
from £689pp
SEE MORE DETAIL...
New York
from £669pp
SEE MORE DETAIL...
Follow Us On Social Media
Opening Times
Monday - Friday
09:00 - 18:00
Saturday
09:00 - 17:00
Sunday
10:00 - 17:00
HomeHoliday Types
Family HolidaysLuxury HolidaysMotorhome HolidaysVilla Package HolidaysHotel HolidaysCondo & Apartment HolidaysTwin Centre HolidaysMulti Centre HolidaysCruise & Stay DealsFly DriveEscorted TouringDestinations
DisneyOrlandoKissimmeeUniversalGulf CoastRest of FloridaThe Deep South, USACaliforniaCanadaDubaiNew YorkLas Vegas & NevadaHawaii HolidaysMore USAMexicoCaribbeanDestination FocusExclusive OffersLuxury CaribbeanExtras
Attraction TicketsBritish AirwaysCar HireCruise America MotorhomesMy Ultimate Las VegasThe SeaWorld ParksOnline Check-InSimon ShoppingUnited AirlinesVoyager Travel InsuranceOur ReviewsBlogCaribbean Collection
